# Martin Reboredo

# **Frontend Web Developer**

**EU/ Spanish Nationality** 

Barcelona +34 677 28 37 16

contacto@martinreboredo.com



www.martinReboredo.com

+5 years of Web Development experience, designing and creating websites using a wide variety of technologies. Currently I am working on my React skills and learning the MERN fullstack. My goal is to deliver meaningful experiences and to work in an agile company with an amazing team of people where I will develop my full potential.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### **SEO Webmaster**

#### www.edreamsodigeo.com, Barcelona, 2018-Present

Create landing pages, participate in QA, work on the front end of internal tools. Improve search results by creating pages with Rich Snippets Text for the 4 travel brands of the company. (Edreams, Opodo, Govoyages, Travellink)

- Develop more than 150 SEO compliant Landing Pages
- Implement Automated QA process for Validate Pages including Lighthouse, W3C, CSS autoprefix, and crossbrowser compatibility.

## Web Developer

### www.aguafy.com, Mexico City, 2016–2017

Created Website and included a marketing plan with several landing pages for Ads.

• Render optimization and cross browser compatibility with a 100% responsive interface and optimized UX/UI and SEO/SEM

# **Marketing Manager**

#### www.playbusiness.mx, Mexico City, 2016-2017

Lead a Marketing Team of 5 extraordinary people. Play Business is the biggest Equity Crowdfunding Firm and Company Builder in LATAM.

- Product Development using Agile/Scrum methodology, MVPs
- Launched Marketing Campaigns with 20% visitors growth monthly rate.

#### Webmaster

#### www.exclusivasfaro.com, Mexico City, 2013-2016

Created and implemented the company online presence using different technologies (ERP, Responsive Web development, Prestashop, etc...).

• +400% ROI in implemented strategy and +5% sales growth

#### Cofounder

## Info Party London, UK, 2007-2013

Lead Ads and Promotions Agency with more than 20 associates, organizing simultaneously marketing and Digital Ads campaigns for 14 clients.

# **SKILLS**

### **Programing Languages**

HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript ES6

#### Libraries

React 16.6, Bootstrap 4, JQuery,

(Currently learning MEARN stack)

#### **Dev Tools & Tech**

Node, Npm, Webpack, Babel, SASS, SCSS, Rest APIs, Github, Chrome DevTools, cPanel, FTP, lazyload,

#### Other tools Tech

JIRA, Asana, Slack, Trello , Photoshop, Illustrator, Google Adwords & Analytics, Facebook Ads, Google Webmaster Tools, Lighthouse, ...

#### Methodology

Agile/KANBAN, UX/UI, SEO/SEM, Lean, W3C,

## CMS - ERP

Prestashop & Dolibar & Wordpress

### **Speaking Languages**

English 100%, Spanish 100%, Portuguese 50%

## **HIGHLIGHTS**

Experience in **Startup Crowdfunding** & Fintech Authored article in Expansión magazine (MX). Taught Digital Marketing in Anahuac University

## **EDUCATION**

Fullstack Web Development, (present) freeCodeCamp, Udemy, LinkedIN, MOOC's. Frontend Nanodegree, Udacity, (2016)

Master in Business Administration, (2013)

University of Roehampton, London, UK. Metropolitan University, London, UK.

Bachelor of Business Administration, (2004) University of Wales, IESIDE, Vigo, Spain.